Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 14 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a mountain in Tibet], 15
    - [Tibetan man looking at the water], 16
    - [A herd of yaks in Tibet], 17
    - [A stone arch in the mountains of Tibet], 18
    - [A home (?) made of stone in Tibet], 19
    - [a Tibetan man preparing food], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas watching a man cook food in Tibet], 21
    - [People sitting down for a meal inTibet], 22
    - [A vendor at a marketplace in Tibet, 23
    - [A Tibetan person weaving thread], 24
    - [Two Tibetan people], 25
    - [A Tibetan man holding two dogs], 26
    - [Two Tibetan women holding goods], 27
    - [A Tibetan family], 28
    - [A Tibetan man and woman], 29
    - [A Tibetan mans itting outside of his home, praying (?)], 30
    - [A young Tibetan man sitting on a blanket], 31
    - [A Tibetan man sticking out his tounge], 32
    - [A Tibetan man on the road to a city], 33
    - [A Tibetan man carrying bags on the road], 34
    - [A Tibetan man sticking out his tounge], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting on a rock, looking at the water in Tibet], 36
    - [A yak grazing in Tibet], 37
    - [Two men and a few yaks in Tibet], 38
    - [Yaks grazing in Tibet], 39
    - [Man with a group of yaks grazing in a field in Tibet], 40
    - [Man and woman with a yak in Tibet], 41
    - [Yaks carrying supplies in Tibet], 42
    - [Yaks walking up a hill in Tibet], 43
    - [People and yaks around a tent in Tibet], 44
    - [Man walking with two yaks in Tibet], 45
    - [Man with yaks in Tibet], 46
    - [Men and donkeys carrying supplies through a river in Tibet], 47
    - [Men riding on donkeys in Tibet], 48
    - [Men riding doneys carrying supplies through water in Tibet], 49
    - [Man sitting on a donkey in Tibet], 50
    - [Donkeys with supplies taking a break near water in Tibet], 51
    - [Man with horse walking up rocks in Tibet], 52
    - [Men and donkeys carrying supplies through a river in Tibet], 53
    - [Group of donkeys carrying supplies across a river in Tibet], 54
    - [Man standing with a horse on the side of a trail in Tibet], 55
    - [Donkey caravan walking on a path by a river in Tibet], 56
    - [Two men carrying supplies through water in Tibet], 57
    - [Donkey caravan walking through a river in Tibet], 58
    - [Donkey being pulled up the rocks in Tibet], 59
    - [Donkey caravan in Tibet coming out of the water], 60
    - [Donkey caravan walking through a river in Tibet], 61
    - [Shrine (?) in Tibet], 62
    - [Tibetan people getting supplies out of yak-skin boats], 63
    - [Tibetan people in yak-skin boats], 64
    - [Tibetan man rowing a boat with supplies], 65
    - [Tibetan man rowing a yak-skin boat with passengers], 66
    - [Tibetan man rowing a yak-skin boat], 67
    - [Tibetan man rowing a yak-skin boat with supplies], 68
    - [Lowell Thomas in a yak-skin boat with others in Tibet], 69
    - [Lowell Thomas riding in a yak-skin boat in Tibet], 70
    - [Lowell Thomas and others in a yak-skin boat], 71
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 15 (Box 1578)
    - [People riding in a yak-skin boat in Tibet], 1
    - [People unloading from yak-skin boats in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan people unloading supplies from yak-skinned boats], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas going through supplies in Tibet], 4
    - [Yak-skin boats drying out in Tibet], 5
    - [Man carrying a yak-skin boat in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan people gathered around the shore], 7
    - [Man riding donkeys through the water in Tibet], 8
    - [Caravan going through the water in Tibet], 9
    - [Tibetan man rowing a yak-skinned boat], 10
    - [A street in a city in Tibet], 11
    - [City street in Tibet], 12
    - [Yaks sitting outside of a building in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan people gathered in a city], 14
    - [Markets on the side of a city street in Tibet], 15
    - [Man looking at goods in a marketplace in Tibet], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at a necklace in a market in Tibet], 17
    - [People walking around a marketplace in Tibet], 18
    - [Tibetan people in a marketplace], 19
    - [People in a marketplace in Tibet], 20
    - [Tibetan people on a city street], 21
    - [Goods in a marketplace in Tibet], 22
    - [People carrying sticks in Tibet], 23
    - [Men sitting with rocks in Tibet], 24
    - [Tibetan people surrounding a vendor on the street], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a salesman in Tibet], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting in a shop with others in Tibet], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas holding an abacus in a shop in Tibet], 28
    - [Tibetan people lined up in the street], 29
    - [Tibetan man wearing a hat], 30
    - [People outside of a building in Tibet], 31
    - [People sitting (praying?) in Tibet], 32
    - [Tibetan people sitting by the water], 33
    - [Tibetan people walking down a dirt road], 34
    - [People walking around in Tibet], 35
    - [Man standing under a canvas in Tibet], 36
    - [Crowd gathered around a tent in Tibet], 37
    - [A crowd watching a performance in Tibet], 38
    - [A performer wearing a mask in Tibet], 39
    - [A crowd watching performers in Tibet], 40
    - [Performers in Tibet], 41
    - [A large crowd watching a performance in Tibet], 42
    - [People performing in Tibet], 43
    - [Performers with masks in Tibet], 44
    - [Two performers in Tibet], 45
    - [Tibetan soldiers], 46
    - [Performers wearing masks in Tibet], 47
    - [A crowd watching a performance in Tibet], 48
    - [Tibetan soldiers marching down a street], 49
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with three Tibetan people], 50
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in a garden with Tibetan woman and children], 51
    - [Tibetan monk (?)], 52
    - [Lowell Thomas taking a bath in a tin basin], 53
    - [Tibetan monks walking down a stone road], 54
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two Tibetan monks], 55
    - [Man painting in Tibet], 56
    - [Tibetan man painting], 57
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men in Tibet], 58
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with four Tibetan monks], 59
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a Tibetan man on a horse], 60
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a Tibetan family], 61
    - [Military persons in Tibet], 62
    - [Tibetan soldier], 63
    - [Three men in Tibet], 64
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two Tibetan man and a donkey], 65
    - [Tibetan soldier wearing tiger fur], 66
    - [Tibetan soldiers (?) marching a playing drums], 67
    - [Tibetan soldiers], 68
    - [Tibetan man with two women and a child], 69
    - [Three Tibetan people in a garden], 70
    - [Man in a suit standing with three Tibetan women], 71
    - [Tibetan mother and child], 72
    - [Three men (?) sitting on a rug in Tibet], 73
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two men in Tibet], 74
    - [Men walking down a stone road in Tibet], 75
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with two Tibetan men], 76
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 16 (Box 1578)
    - [Two Tibetan monks], 1
    - [Tibetan monks riding on horses], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sharing a meal with monks in Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas eating with Tibetan monks], 4
    - [Two Tibetan men and women], 5
    - [Man in a suit standing with a Tibetan monk holding a flower], 6
    - [City at the base of mountains in Tibet], 7
    - [City buildings at the base of a mountain in Tibet], 8
    - [City in Tibet], 9
    - [People walking down a narrow street in a city in Tibet], 10
    - [Monks gathered in a square in Tibet], 11
    - [Tibetan monks kneeling in a Square], 12
    - [Young Tibetan monks gatheres around a stage], 13
    - [Monks gathered in Tibet], 14
    - [Monks performing a ceremony in Tibet (?)], 15
    - [Monks in Tibet during a ceremony (?)], 16
    - [Monks in Tibet during a ceremony (?)], 17
    - [Tibetan monks kneeling before a monk with a hat], 18
    - [Tibetan monks kneeling and a monk with a hat standing], 19
    - [Elderly monks in Tibet], 20
    - [Young Tibetan monks holding yellow hats], 21
    - [Three monks in Tibet], 22
    - [Open space in a monk monestary], 23
    - [Tibetan monk], 24
    - [Tibetan monk smiling], 25
    - [Tibetan monk standing outside of an ornate door], 26
    - [Tibetan monk outside of an ornate door], 27
    - [Calendar (?) Chart (?) in a monestary in Tibet], 28
    - [Statue in a monestary in Tibet], 29
    - [Shrine in a monestary in Tibet], 30
    - [Shrine in a monestary in Tibet], 31
    - [Shrine in a monestary in Tibet], 32
    - [Monk monestary in Tibet], 33
    - [Buddist prayer tree in Tibetan monestary], 34
    - [Monks at a monestary in Tibet], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Tibetan monks], 36
    - [Tibetan monk at a monestary], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at items at a vendor in Tibet], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at goods in Tibet], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas inspecting an item in Tibet], 40
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at an item in Tibet (not a full picture?)], 41
    - [Ivory sculptures and other goods in Tibet], 42
    - [The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 43
    - [The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 44
    - [The Dalai Lama with others in Tibet], 45
    - [The Dalai Lama with others in Tibet], 46
    - [The Dalai Lame with two others surrounded by flowers], 47
    - [Tibetan monks], 48
    - [Two Tibetan monks], 49
    - [Lowell Thomas with five Tibetan monks], 50
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing with five Tibetan monks], 51
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Dalai Lama in Tibet], 52
    - [The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 53
    - [Lowell Thomas with Tibetan monks], 54
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with Tibetan monks], 55
    - [Tibetan monk], 56
    - [Tibetan monks at a monestary], 57
    - [Four Tibetan monks at a monestary], 58
    - [The Dalai Lama with other monks], 59
    - [Lowell Thomas with two monks in Tibet], 60
    - [A group of people in Tibet], 61
    - [Lowell Thomas with a family (?) in Tibet], 62
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a Tibetan family], 63
    - [Three Tibetan people], 64
    - [Young Tibetan monk], 65
    - [Lowell Thomas kneeling next to a young Tibetan monk], 66
    - [The Potala Palace in Tibet], 67
    - [The Potala Palace in Tibet], 68
    - [The Potala Palace in Tibet], 69
    - [Two men on horses walking in front of the Potala Palace], 70
    - [People gathered in front of a lake, the Potala Palace in the background, Tibet], 71
    - [People walking towards the Potala Palace in Tibet], 72
    - [The Potala Palace, Tibet], 73
    - [People gathered in front of the Potala Palace, Tibet], 74
    - [People walking up the steps to the Potala Palace, Tibet], 75
    - [Lowell Thomas at the Potala Palace in Tibet], 76
    - [Statue (?) in the Potala Palace in Tibet], 77
    - [Tibetan monk in a monestary], 78
    - [Tibetan monk hitting a drum], 79
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 17 (Box 1578)
    - [Man standing by a prayer tree in Tibet], 1
    - [Tibetan monk blowing a horn], 2
    - [Men riding on horses in Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and his group in Tibet], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and his group gathered in a field in Tibet], 5
    - [Herd of yaks (?) in a field in Tibet, snowy mountains in the background], 6
    - [Scenic view of snowy mountains and fields in Tibet], 7
    - [Snowy mountains and a field in Tibet], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outside a house in Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outside a house in Tibet], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas conducting an interview outside of a house in Tibet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at notes in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. preparing for a broadcast in Tibet], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. preparing the recording equipment for a broadcast in Tibet], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing a man in Tibet], 15
    - [Man in a suit standing next to a woman in Tibet], 16
    - [Four men in Tibet], 17
    - [People loading Lowell Thomas's recording equipment into a yak-skinned boat in Tibet], 18
    - [Man on a horse holding Lowell Thomas's recording equipment in Tibet], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas reading his script for a broadcast in Tibet], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a microphone during a broadcast for a man in Tibet], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas holding the microphone for a man during a broadcast in Tibet], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men in Tibet], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing with a few men and a child in Tibet], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting on steps in Tibet], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. speaking with a man in Tibet], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting on steps in Tibet], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr, and another man in Tibet], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man in Tibet], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas and a Tibetan man looking at a document in Tibet], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a Tibetan man], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a horse in Tibet], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a banner, "Lodwick School of Aeronautics", in Tibet], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding a "Lodwick School of Aeronautics" in Tibet], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man in Tibet], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. with a Tibetan man], 36
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in Tibet], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas with people in Tibet], 38
    - [Tibetan men unloading supplies from donkeys], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas's group resting outside of a building in Tibet], 40
    - [View of the mountains in Tibet], 41
    - [Donkey caravan going through Tibet], 42
    - [A herd of yaks grazing in a field in Tibet], 43
    - [Lowell Thomas riding on a donkey at the head of the caravan in Tibet], 44
    - [Man riding a donkey through the mountains of Tibet], 45
    - [Donkeys walking through the mountains in Tibet], 46
    - [Donkeys walking on a path through the mountains of Tibet], 47
    - [Lowell Thomas's caravan on a path through the mountains in Tibet], 48
    - [Donkey caravan walking on a path in the mountains in Tibet], 49
    - [Lowell Thomas's donkey caravan walking through the mountains of Tibet], 50
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a donkey, walking on a mountain trail in Tibet], 51
    - [Two Tibetan men walking on a trail in the mountains], 52
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a horse on the side of a trail in Tibet], 53
    - [View of the trail in Tibet from a donkey], 54
    - [Donkey caravan on a path in the mountains of Tibet], 55
    - [Tibetan man sitting on a rock in the mountaisn of Tibet], 56
    - [Lowell Thomas's caravan in a mountain path in Tibet], 57
    - [Donkeys walking through mountains in Tibet], 58
    - [Lowell Thomas by a prayer tree in Tibet], 59
    - [People walking on the steps of the Potala Palace in Tibet], 60
    - [A group of people gathered by tents in Tibet], 61
    - [Tibetan soldiers playing instruments and marching], 62
    - [Tibetan woman and child standing outside of a shelter], 63
    - [Lowell Thomas and his group in Tibet], 64
    - [Three Tibetan men], 65
    - [Two people standing outside a building in Tibet], 66
    - [Tibetan man selling goods in a marketplace], 67
    - Tibetan man farming], 68
    - [Tibetan people gathered outside of a tent], 69
    - [Tibetan man and woman], 70
    - [A herd of yaks grazing in a field by mountains in Tibet], 71
    - [Donkeys carrying supplies in Tibet], 72
    - [Group of people in Tibet], 73
    - [Small town in Tibet], 74
    - [A herd of yak grazing in Tibet], 75
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting in a sedan chair in Tibet], 76
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a Tibet woman], 77
    - [Tibetan woman in traditional garb (?)], 78
    - [Tibetan man with a large headdress], 79
    - [Scenic view of the mountains and fields of Tibet], 80
    - [Lowell Thomas being carried in a sedan chair in Tibet], 81
    - [Donkeys walking on a bridge over a river in Tibet], 82
    - [A Tibetan monk], 83
    - [Tibetan monks at a monestary during a ceremony (?)], 84
    - [Woman standing next to a Tibetan woman in traditional dress (?)], 85
    - [Lowell Thomas and others in Tibet], 86
    - [People gathered outside of a tent in Tibet], 87
    - [Lowell Thomas with others in Tibet], 88
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 18 (Box 1578)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in Tibet], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas in a sedan chair in Tibet], 2
    - [The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and two Tibetan monks], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. with a young Tibetan monk], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with others in Tibet], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with Tibetan monks in front of the Potala Palace in Tibet], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas with others in Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving something from a Tibetan man], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. listening to a Tibetan monk play a horn], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas with three Tibetan men], 12
    - [Glass sculptures (?) on a table in Tibet], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas on a donkey in Tibet], 14
    - [A young Tibetan monk], 15
    - [A man with a Tibetan woman in tradiational dress (?)], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. talking with two Tibetan men], 17
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr.'s trip to Tibet], 18
    - [Photos of the Potala Palace and other places in Tibet], 19
    - [Photos of Tibetan monks (and the Dalai Lama) in Tibet], 20
    - [The Dalai Lama, unique image], 21
  Box 1579
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Tibet, 1949; 1 (Box 1579)
    - Lamyik, 1
    - Lamyik, 2
    - Lamyik, 3
    - Lamyik, 4
    - Lamyik, 5
    - Lamyik, 6
    - Text of Lamyik, 7
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. in front of a tapestry wearing a fur coat in Tibet], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in front of a tapestry holding goblets (?) in Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a woman standing in front of a tapestry in Tibet], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a woman in front of a tapestry in Tibet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding cups in front of a tapestry in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. in front of a tapestry in Tibet], 13
    - [A group of people in Tibet in front of the Potala Palace], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. in front of a tapestry holding goblets (?) in Tibet], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sipping out of a goblet in Tibet], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in front of a tapestry in Tibet holding goblets (?)], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing in front of a tapestry in a fur coat in Tibet], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thoms Jr. with Tibetan monks standing in front of the Potala Palace], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with Tibetan monks standing in front of the Potala Palace], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with three Tibetan monks standing in front of the Potala Palace], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and three Tibetan monks standing in front of the Potala Palace], 22
  - Subject files: Tibet (Sven Hedin), 1951; 2 (Box 1579)
    - [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Sven Hedin], 1
    - [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Sven Hedin, continued], 2
  - Subject files: Niles Trammel, undated; 3 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving and award from Niles Trammel], 1
  - Subject files: Travel Hall of Fame, circa 1960s; 4 (Box 1579)
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas with three other men], 1
    - Note [Neil Armstrong, L.T., Robert Marley (?), .Travel Hall of Fame], 2
  - Subject files: Travelogue (1,000,000th visitor), circa 1919 - early 1920s; 5 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man in a top hat], 1
    - Note [The Bishop of Gloucester, the millionth visitor to see and hear "With Allenby in Palestine and Lawrence in Arabia" in London, congratulating Lowell Thomas outside the Royal Opera House, Covent Gardens, where Thomas told his strange tale of adventure for nearly a year." (-is it possible to zoom in? the print is so small)], 2
  - Subject files: Travelogue poster (With Allenby in Palestine and with Lawrence in Arabia)], undated; 6 (Box 1579)
    - [Travelogue poster, "With Allenby in Palestine and Lawrence in Arabia", 1
  - Subject files: Trip to China and Tibet, 1977; 7 (Box 1579)
    - Note: Tibetan Dance Troop. Ved Parkash 16A/19WEA New Delhi, 1
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 2
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 3
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 4
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 5
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 6
    - Tibetan children, Dharamsala, 7
    - Tibetan dance troop, 8
    - Note: Tibetan Children Dharamsala. Ved Parkash 16A/19WEA New Delhi, 9
    - Tibetan dance troop, 10
    - Tibetan dance troop, 11
    - Tibetan dance troop, 12
    - Tibetan dance troop, 13
    - Tibetan dance troop, 14
    - Tibetan dance troop, 15
    - Tibetan dance troop, 16
    - Note: 1-8/10 Crop for 2 central figures e n rg [?] Tibet, 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Dalai Lama], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a Tibetan man next to a tree], 19
    - Note: 7/1 cach 8/10 glossy best best cropping for repro, 20
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Tibetan children], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at a map with the Dalai Lama], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with the Dalai Lama], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group children], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with aJawaharlal Nehru (?)], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas with the Dalai Lama], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas with two Tibetan men], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas with Norman Rockwell], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas with Norman Rockwell], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three men in traditional costumes], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas walking with a group of children, Tibet (?)], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting and speaking with a Tibetan man (?)], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas with Norman Rockwell], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas with Jawaharlal Nehru], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas with Jawaharlal Nehru], 35
  - Subject Files: Trip to China and Tibet, 1977; 8 (Box 1579)
    - Note: At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 1
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 2
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 3
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 4
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 5
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 6
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 7
    - At the American Embassy, New Delhi., 8
    - Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi., 9
    - Note: Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi., 10
    - Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi., 11
    - Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi., 12
    - Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi., 13
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 14
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 15
    - Note: With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 16
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 17
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 18
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 19
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, 20
    - With Dalai Lama, Dharamsala, playing with dog, 21
    - Dharamsala, 22
    - Dharamsala, 23
    - Dharamsala, 24
    - Dharamsala, 25
    - Dharamsala, 26
    - Dharamsala, 27
    - Dharamsala, 28
    - Dharamsala, 29
    - Dharamsala, 30
    - Dharamsala, 31
    - Dharamsala, 32
    - Dharamsala, 33
    - Dharamsala, 34
    - Dharamsala, 35
    - Note: At the American Embassy, New Delhi, 36
    - Note: Acharya J. B. Kriplani, J.J. Singh at New Delhi, 37
    - Note: Pix with the Dalai Lama Dharamsala., 38
    - Note: Pix at Dharamsala India., 39
  - Subject Files: Trip to China and Tibet, 1977; 9 (Box 1579)
    - Note: Pix with Nehru & Pix with Dr. Gill, New Delhi, 1
    - Lowell Thomas talking with a man in Tibet, 2
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with a man in Tibet, 3
    - Note: Tibetan Children, Dharamsala, 4
    - Tibetan Children, Dharamsala, 5
    - Tibetan Children, Dharamsala, 6
    - Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 7
    - Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 8
    - Lowell Thomas walking with the children at the Tibetan Refugee Nursery, 9